PROPHECY TIME
How are you?
Where is your wife?
She was in the church.
She went for a meeting right now.
That is your first wife.
It is my wife, my only wife.
I want to see you.
OK, sir.
Because there is a controversy.
STANDARD FOR LIFE
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
Wow!
My name is Henry Nwajames.
The person beside me is my lovely wife.
As you saw from the telecast on that fateful day, the servant of Jesus Christ Prophet T.B. Joshua
was moving about.
As he was coming towards me, inside me I was praying that this servant of God will talk to me.
I was thinking about how he would speak about my breakthrough - my millions and my businesses -
not knowing that he would take me to a different direction.
When he eventually got to me, he asked if he could speak to me.
I told him that he could go ahead and speak to me.
He asked about my wife and my wife had just left for a meeting.
I told him that my wife had just left for a meeting. He said, "Your first wife".
I could not understand.
Before I knew it, he said, "There is a controversy".
As God would have it, before I could get to my house that fateful day, my wife had returned from the meeting,
my mother-in-law and brothers and sisters were all in the house.
They were watching Emmanuel TV.
As I left the church, I didn't understand anything.
My mind didn't even take me to where the Holy Spirit was taking me.
When I got home, the woman shouted, "Didn't you know what to tell the man of God?"
She asked if I had forgotten the story I told her about my daughter somewhere.
I said, "Oh, are you sure that is what the man of God is talking about?"
I said, "But I don't know how to go about it".
I had to contact my cousin who was the only person who knew about the issue.
It was in those early days when I was a child.
I did disco jockeying in those days.
On my father's side is very close to where I used to do disco jockeying.
That is the place I used to meet with this young lady who begot this girl.
So, when this matter happened - not that I didn't hear about it - my brother came and told me
that the girl was pregnant.
He asked me: "What do we do about it?"
He said: "Since that is the case, you have to rush away from here
because everybody knows that this place is your maternal home.
If this thing happens, I don't know what will happen next".
That is how I ran away from my father's place and maternal home.
I unwillingly gave her my cousin's telephone number.
When she called the young man, he said: "Right now, I don't know how to trace this girl
but give me some time; I will know what to do about it".
One day, my cousin called me that the aunty to my daughter was late and that it was an opportunity
for me to see her.
I told him that when he saw her, he should let me know.
The young man called us later on and told us that he had got her number and information about her.
Before I knew it, he called me and said that this lady's husband had just died.
He said that that was the information that he had just got now.
I said: "Wow", and then he said: "What should we do?"
I replied: "This is an opportunity for us to see her".
Before we knew it, one day he called me to say he had called the girl she was coming and that we should come.
I was unwillingly to go but my wife insisted that I should come.
She said: "Let me go and see. Do you want me to die in poverty?"
I said that I was sorry and that she should go and find out.
I was in my house and my wife called me back to say that people were crying and shouting,
saying: "Look, at what you have done".
I said that I was very sorry, that she should help me to tell her that I was sorry.
Regarding the controversy that the man of God was talking about,
the husband that died needed to be buried on the 27th of December.
I said that I would send my wife and family but when they got there, the burial was no longer conducted
which is the controversy that the man of God was talking about.
When they came back, I was told that a letter had come from the court, asking them to leave the house,
that the children and wife no longer belong to the husband.
I did not understand.
Hallelujah. We have been listening to the experience of Mr. Henry Nwajames, to his explaining that
the prophecy he received from Prophet T.B. Joshua concerning his first wife and a controversy is very true.
When he was young man, long time before he got married, he had a relationship with a lady.
He was very young at that time.
The lady became pregnant but because of the shame and everything attached to that he denied that baby
and the entire family also denied that baby.
He said that when the man of God mentioned this to him he didn't even think about it.
It was only a friend who reminded him that he had told him a story about how he had impregnated a lady
when he was very very small.
Since that time he could not trace the girl, he had never seen the girl, he had no fatherly relation with the girl.
In fact he didn't even know where the girl was.
After the man's of God prophecy, he asked the particular family member who knew about the case
to try and trace this particular girl and found out that she had married but her husband had just died
and there was a lot of controversy surrounding the death of her husband, and the burial was unable to hold.
People were even accusing this girl of being behind her husband's death.
This thing happened about 28 years ago and I've not seen this girl with my eyes
'til today when I invited my cousin to help me trace her.
We are in the church now and it is the first time I am meeting her.
This situation has actually held him in bondage for many years.
The business collapsed, everything collapsed.
He had been struggling to get it right - no way.
But he never thought there was something, somewhere.
Not, until this prophetic word.
The child is inside the church now - he has never seen this child.
Let the child come out.|
For how many years?
For 28 years.
... you saw her last?
I've not seen her before.
You don't even know her?
Yes, sir.
Mr Henry Nwajames' Daughter & Grandchildren
Look at the woman and at this man.
Mr Henry Nwajames & Family
Prophecy Confirmation
Can you see the picture of both of them?
Mr Henry Nwajames & Family
Prophecy Confirmation
See those two faces.
Mr Henry Nwajames & Family
Prophecy Confirmation
Can you stand up and tell God, "God, reveal my own"?
[God, reveal my own.]
Stand up!
Mr Henry Nwajames & Family
Prophecy Confirmation
Stand up.
Let God reveal your own.
The father and the daughter are there now.
They don't know whether to hug themselves or to greet themselves...
The lady started to cry.
Mr Henry Nwajames & Family
Prophecy Confirmation
Who is this man?
He is my cousin.
He is the one that knows our secret.
Thank you.
They are your children.
Yes, sir.
You have to forgive your dad because this is by revelation not by human hands.
It has been your prayer.
What have been your prayers before now?
All my life, I have been praying to see him.
All your life you have been praying to see him?
But your mommy gave you some pictures in the past.
She didn't tell anything.
Your mommy didn't tell you anything?
Yes, sir.
All my life, I have been staying with my grandmother.
That is, the person that I took as my mother but I didn't know she was my grandmother.
So, she died here in 1999.
That was when I came to Lagos to stay with her son and his wife.
The family did not register me for the SSCE exam.
One day, I was having an issue with them, so the wife called me a bastard.
The husband then said that I behave like my father.
So, I ran away from the house and went to meet my uncle because he lives closer to the house.
So, I told my uncle what the man had said, calling me a bastard and asked him if he knew anything about it
or if not, I would kill myself or I would run away from the house.
He told me that I had a father but it was a secret.
I asked him what kind of secret could he not tell me about in my situation.
He replied that it was a secret that nobody knew about except him, my mother and my father.
I said: "OK, if you cannot tell me anything about it, it is better for me to run away".
So, I run away from his house.
Unfortunately, the husband and wife found out where I was living.
After my SSCE exam, she has a restaurant in Lagos island,
and she said I should help her sell in her beer parlour, restaurant.
There was where I was staying with her and helping her to sell.
All through those days, I was crying and weeping because I was going through trials and temptation.
At any little thing that I did, she would repeat that I was a bastard.
Anywhere I was, I would be telling God: "I need to know where I come from".
She then introduced me to one man who is my husband now.
She said that I should go and marry him.
At that time, I was only 16 years old.
OK, it is all right.
What would you...?
You have... I don't know - this is your daughter.
Man of God, please...
Stand up.
I don't know.
I think I need to sit...
And these are your children?
Yes, sir.
This is my first born and this is the second born.
So, we thank God for this revelation.
The name of God is so wonderful.
This is a job for you.
Since God has shown so much mercy and kindness, ... I don't know.
So, help me to take them to the round table.
The father will do the right thing over there, not in an open space here, OK?
My daughter, please.
Thank you very much.
Mr Henry Nwajames & Family
Prophecy Confirmation
The reconciliation will not happen in the place where you or me will be.
TESTIMONY TIME
Mr. Nwajames with his family, daughter and grandchildren were taken to a quiet,
pleasant environment, where they could have some privacy and enjoy their first meal together.
Now, they have been reunited as a family through the prophetic revelation of Prophet T.B. Joshua.
Served with some rice and freshly squeezed orange juice they were ready to begin.
But before the meal, the family had something to say.
My name is Henry Nwajames.
The person by my side is my lovely wedded wife.
The person on my left side is my found daughter, whom I am just seeing for the first time after 28 years.
The brother here is my cousin who knows a little bit about us.
When we were playing all these pranks in those days when we were kids, he used to be there with me.
These are my grandchildren.
You can see how beautiful they are.
This is a blessing.
She is my daughter's first daughter and this is Uche, the son.
What brought me to The SCOAN was the prophecy that the man of God gave me sometime in 2012.
The man of God walked up to me.
I had prayed: "I want this man of God to meet me today; I want this man of God to speak to my situation".
I thought he was going to tell me that I would win the contract or that my millions would come tomorrow
but when he came to me, it hit me in a way that I could not understand.
He asked me where my wife was.
I replied that my wife had left for a meeting, right from the church.
He said that he meant my very first wife.
I told him that I have one wife and that she was my only wife.
He said that there was a controversy.
I could not understand or even remember that I once had an encounter sometime, somewhere.
I did not think that the prophecy had anything to do with me having abandoned my daughter.
When I got home, my wife who was not in the church at that moment, had already returned from her meeting.
So, she was at home with my mother, my other children and relations.
They were all watching Emmanuel TV and saw the whole thing.
When I got home, my wife pounced on me and asked me: "Have you forgotten the story you told me?
Where is the telephone number of your cousin?"
She asked me if I had forgotten about the girl I told her about.
I said: "No, the man of God did not say so. I did not marry her".
She said: "No, what the man of God said is not too far from this thing".
It was then that I took out my cousin's telephone number and she started calling my cousin immediately.
I didn't know that what had 'brushed' me down and shattered me was my ignorance at this big mistake
which I never knew.
Meanwhile on my own side, this had affected me tremendously.
I could not even understand myself anymore.
I was a big boy; I was doing so well.
I had projects in my village; I was the first to build a storied building.
At the end, I was selling my properties.
I had landed properties and sold all.
I went overseas and brought this and that but at the end of the day, I could not account for anything.
As I was coming to the church, I was praying that God would open my way
and show me the root cause of my problem.
As God would have it, that fateful day, the man of God prophesied to me.
When we got home, we focused on the prophecy and started looking for this girl
and that was how this discovery came about.
I thank God today that she is here and I have been appealing to her to forgive me.
This was what I did out of ignorance as a young man.
That time, I was afraid that if my relations saw me, they would kill me
or tell me that I had committed one abomination or the other.
That was why I left, not knowing that, that place was where my dad's mum came from.
I could have married from that village.
The only family I could not have married into was my cousin's family.
My mind was strengthened and I knew that God had forgiven me.
I didn't care what anybody would say.
My cousin, on his own part did his best because he always told me that
I was the only one that knew about this child and that I should not forget.
When he texted me, I didn't take it seriously.
My daughter, I'm very sorry.
I know I've sinned before God and before people.
But please, I am appealing to you, my daughter; forgive me.
Now that I have seen my daughter for the first time, after all these years, it is a fulfilled day.
I am happy.
My daughter, please, forgive me.
I am very sorry, my daughter, please, forgive me!
I promise to carry you along.
As far as I have seen you, nothing whatsoever will separate us anymore as long as the love of God
is working in our lives.
My daughter!
Thank You, Jesus Christ!
Thank You, Lord!
My name is Chidindu.
I am so happy.
I don't know what to say.
I thank God for today that He has made it possible for me to see a day like this.
I don't know how to say it.
I am overwhelmed.
I am so happy because all of my life, I didn't even know what a father was.
I had never ever tasted fatherly love.
Sometimes, I would go to my friends' houses;
their fathers would pamper them and I would ask God: "Who is my father?"
But today, God made it possible for me to see my father and mother.
She is my mother because without her, this would never had happened.
It is not every woman who can go through this and still fish out the person they had been looking for.
I will never ever in this life forget her because I am so happy.
Sometime ago, my husband used to ask me: "Are you sure you are going to see your father?"
I replied that he should not worry that one day, I would see my father.
This is unfortunate that he doesn't witness it today.
I am so happy.
Despite all that I have been through all my life, today, I am so happy!
God used the man of God to prophesy my case.
I was not here but God used him to prophecy my case.
I am so happy and I thank God and every member of this church who helped and witnessed today.
From today, I have forgiven my father.
I promise to remain your dad.
You are my first daughter.
We used to call a first daughter in my place, 'Ada'.
She is 'Ada'.
My name is Eddie Anyiam.
I thank God for today.
I witnessed my brother and his daughter.
I was there when the whole thing happened.
I promised my sister that I would keep the secret for security reasons, which I did.
Since then, things had not been easy for me because I was carrying a load that I was not able to bear.
One day, my sister came to me and told me that she did not want to go back to her uncle again.
I asked her why and whether there was any problem.
She replied that I would not understand.
I asked her why she said that I would not understand, that she should tell me.
She replied that she would not tell me.
We started to argue and she said that if I didn't want her to stay in my house, she would go.
I said: "Please, don't leave; let me settle this matter".
She said she didn't want to go to that place anymore, that she wanted to stay with me –
to take me as her brother – everything.
She said that those people were calling her a bastard.
When I heard that, I wondered why they were calling this young girl by that name,
was it because her mother was dead.
I told her that she was not a bastard and that she should calm down.
She told me that if she continued to go to that place, she would run away and commit suicide or drink poison.
I asked her not to kill herself, that I knew her dad, that she should keep the secret.
Today, I am happy that God has revealed the secret and I am happy that I have seen my brother.
I thank God for my brother's wife; she made it possible for us to be together.
This is my first time of coming to this church.
I lost my wife over five years ago.
I have one boy and one girl and I am not finding things easy.
I don’t know whether it was the curse of my sister, here that was causing me disappointment in life.
People would make promises to me but in the end, they would disappoint me.
But I thank God that the bondage has been removed.
I thank God for the man of God and for my cousin's wife and for my junior sister.
It is well.
From today I am a member of this church.
I have seen the work of God here.
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Ijeoma Nwajames.
I want to thank God for today because God has made it happen in my life.
I see these things happening in other families.
I have seen miracles since I've been watching Emmanuel TV.
This is a family, that when I entered into it newly in marriage, everything was there for me.
Money was there and fleets of cars.
I had pleasures.
I didn't know that the world could change all of a sudden.
I didn't know what was happening.
As I was living in luxury, I had seven biological children.
I didn't know that one day, I would be begging for food to take care of those children.
All of a sudden, everything started withering – going down.
We were all wondering.
Then, we didn't know about Emmanuel TV.
We were wondering what was happening.
We have attended a lot of churches.
Some churches we attended did some sacrifices.
A lot of things had happened in our lives.
We didn't know what was really happening.
When the man of God gave the prophecy, I called him,
though I was not in the church by the time the prophecy came.
I asked him about his first wife.
He said that he didn't have a first wife.
I reminded him about the story he told me.
We were praying that God would visit us the way He had visited other people.
When he told me about it, I told him that the prophecy was talking about this child, though the mother was late.
He said: "But the man of God did not say the controversy was about a child".
I said: "Do you want him to explain everything when you have already told him that you don't have a first wife?"
I understand what is happening and we have been watching Emmanuel TV
for a long time, that the man of God speaks in parables.
He had spoken it and it was all about this child.
I went and met the girl.
That day I met the girl, something spoke to my heart that the whole thing had come to an end.
Something told me that she was the daughter.
I held her and she was crying that: "So, I have a wonderful mum like this".
She held onto me and since that day, we have been talking; I kept calling her.
I try to show her love and today, everything has come to pass that this family has been united -
she has met her dad and the dad has met his daughter.
I called my daughter when I got home that day.
I said: "We have another 'Ada' somewhere."
She said: "How can it be?"
I said: "Daddy has another 'Ada' (first daughter) somewhere; that means you are no longer 'Ada'."
She said: "If daddy is truly the person who had the child, I don't have to argue about it;
she remains 'Ada' I am 'sister humble'."
We laughed.
Today, I know that when my children meet them, they will be glad
because they are all part of the Emmanuel TV family.
We are all happy to witness this happening today in our lives.
We accept you with our whole hearts and everything is yours.
My wonderful grandchildren – I am ready to serve these children from today.
Today is a new day in my life and family.
I am so happy about what the man of God is doing in this place.
I am a staunch follower of T.B. Joshua and I will continue to follow him 'til the end of the world.
It is certain that nothing can separate us.
I am very happy today and pray that as we reunite today, this family will remain in unity,
in the name of Jesus Christ!
As God continues to use T.B. Joshua to do the work of charity and humanity,
the Lord will continue to empower him and refresh him the more.
I pray that God will build this church and the gates of hell shall not prevail, in the name of Jesus Christ!
I want to thank Emmanuel TV Partners – you are wonderful people.
I appreciate and applaud you.
Thank You, Jesus Christ!
In Jesus’ name we pray!
Emmanuel!
(God With Us – Matthew 1:23)
Cheers.
Thank you, my children.
Mr Henry Nwajames & Family
Prophecy Confirmation
This is the day that the Lord has made
We will rejoice and be glad in it
Thank you.
They begin their meal and it's time for Mr. Henry to show his fatherly side,
as he gives a spoon full of rice to his first daughter, receives his own
and then gives another to each of his grandchildren.
A new relationship has been established.
A new home has been built and this family has been restored to the glory of God.
Hallelujah.
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe, to witness more of God’s power at work in our generation today,
and stay up to date with the latest prophecies, deliverances, sermons, and testimonies from SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV - Changing lives, Changing nations and Changing the world.
TT: Robert Begier
RV: Pavel Tatyana Zheleznyakov 27/06/2018